ptk.org 2015-06-07

# Privacy Policy | Phi Theta Kappa Honor Society

Pages within the Phi Theta Kappa website may contain links to sites operated by other entities, whose information distribution practices may differ from Phi Theta Kappa's. Visitors should consult the other sites' privacy notices to determine their policy as to information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties. Phi Theta Kappa cannot control or be held responsible for information distribution practices of websites other than our own.

We do not collect personal information on anonymous visitors to our site. Any statistical information gathered is used in statistical form to shape our site to match our users' needs. When members log in to the exclusive Members section, they are asked to volunteer information that helps inform choices of member benefits.

The following member profile information may be shared with our Corporate Partners and benefits providers, to provide members with relevant scholarship and benefit information: 

  * Induction Date
  * Name
  * Mailing Address
  * Phone Number
  * Institution Name
  * Anticipated Graduation Date
  * Major
  * GPA
  * Email Address

You may opt out of sharing this information at any time by calling Key Services at 1.800.946.9995.

You may correspond with us at the following street address or email requesting access to or correction of your personally identifiable information. For verification purposes please include your first name, last name, email address, chapter and community college.

Phi Theta Kappa International Honor Society  
P.O. Box 13729  
Jackson, MS  
39236-3729  

This privacy policy is subject to change.

2/14/14
